{"data":[{"question":"The experts ___ the problem for quite some time, but they ___ any solutions yet.","a":"have discussed, haven't been finding","b":"have been discussing, haven't found","c":"had discussed, haven't found","d":"discussed, haven't found","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Present perect tense: We use the Present Perfect to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now. We CAN use the Present Perfect with unspecific expressions such as: ever, never, once, many times, several times, before, so far, already, yet, etc. \n- Present perfect continuous: We use the Present Perfect Continuous to show that something started in the past and has continued up until now (they haven't found yet) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Be quiet! I'm trying to hear what the man ___.","a":"is saying","b":"says","c":"has said","d":"said","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Present continuous: express the idea that something is happening now","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Timmy ___ the same motion.","a":"is often doing","b":"is always done","c":"will always do","d":"is always doing","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple future tense: express the idea of a general prediction about the future.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Are the guests about to have dinner? \"Yes, it ___ in the dining room.\"","a":"serves","b":"is serving","c":"served","d":"is being served","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Passive voice \n- Present continuous: express the idea that something is happening now","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Where ___ when Lily was in the hospital?","a":"you were","b":"have you been","c":"are you","d":"were you","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple past tense (same tense with verb \"was\")","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"The suspect will answer for what he ___.","a":"has done","b":"will do","c":"does","d":"had done","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: We use the Present Perfect to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"The washing machine _________ by one of our mechanics right now.","a":"is being repaired","b":"repaired","c":"is going to be repaired","d":"is repaired","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Passive voice \n- Present continuous: express the idea that something is happening now ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"I have to make a phone call. Can you wait a second? It ___ long.","a":"isn't taking","b":"won't be taking","c":"won't take","d":"doesn't take","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple future: express the idea of a general prediction about the future","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Is this the last exam we have to take? \"No, there ___ another two months later.\"","a":"will be","b":"will have been","c":"was","d":"is","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple future: express the idea of a general prediction about the future","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"If you _________ quiet, I'll tell you what's going on.","a":"will be","b":"were","c":"be","d":"are to be","answer":"1","explain":"\n-Zero Conditional: used for habitual actions or accepted facts\nIt is created by if\/when + two clauses with the same tense in each clause.\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"}]}